amen happy Sabbath everyone um we have a
very
special message
today from the word of God and uh the
message will be regarding the mark of
the beast so I want to encourage you to
get your Bibles out because we're going
to be uh going deep into the word of God
today there is a lot of
confusion about this subject of the mark
of the beast and uh we're going to be
looking at what the Bible actually has
to say about this Mark and by the grace
of God we're going to simplify this and
make it so easy that a child could
understand it all right so with that
said we're going to pray and we're going
to jump right into the presentation
Heavenly
Father we ask that you would please
speak to us that you would bless us that
you would open our eyes that we may see
this is our prayer in Jesus name we ask
it amen and
amen let's go to the
screen the subject is entitled once
again the mark of the beast simplified
the mark of the beast simplified and the
first thing we're going to do is we're
going to go to Revelation chapter 13
and we're going to read about the mark
of the beast we're going to read from
Revelation 13 to the end of the chapter
and so let's begin the Bible says in
verse
11 and I beheld another Beast coming up
out of the earth and he had two horns
like a lamb and he spake as a dragon and
he exerciseth all the power of the first
Beast before him and cause the Earth and
them that dwell therein to worship the
first Beast
whose deadly wound was
healed and he doeth great Wonders that
he maketh Fire come down from heaven on
the earth in the sight of men and
deceiveth them that dwell on the Earth
by the means of those Miracles which he
had power to do in the sight of the
Beast saying to them that dwell on the
earth that they should make an image to
the Beast which had the wound by a sword
and did
live and he had power to give life unto
the image of the Beast that the image of
the Beast should both speak and cause
that as many as would not worship the
image of the Beast should be
killed and it causeth all both small and
great rich and poor free and bond to
receive a mark in their right
hand or in their
foreheads verse 17 and that no man might
buy or sell save he that had the Mark or
the name of the Beast or the number of
his name here is wisdom let him that has
understanding count the number of the
Beast for it is the number of a
man and his number is 63 score and6 or
666 and so this is the primary
text that deals with the mark of the
beast and what we're going to do the
first thing we're going to do is we're
going to to uh break down this term the
mark of the
beast so first of all what is a mark a
mark is the same thing as a sign so when
we say a Mark we can simply H uh put in
the place of That Word a sign those who
are marked have a sign that that
connects them with
Satan with the
Antichrist the
Mark or the sign of the Beast is what
there is so much confusion about what is
the sign of the Beast or the mark of the
beast but in order to find that out the
very first thing we need to understand
is what is the
Beast what is the
Beast and we're going to break that down
so if you were to come back to the Book
of Daniel chapter
7 you will see that verse 23 reads this
thus he said the fourth Beast shall be
the fourth Kingdom upon the Earth which
shall be diverse from all kingdoms and
that's all we need to
read for a little bit of background
Daniel chapter 7 records four beasts
coming up out of the sea one is like a
lion the second is like a bear the third
is like a leopard and the fourth Beast
is this nondescript Beast with uh 10
horns and a little horn rising up after
the T horns now we're not left to guess
what these beasts represent because the
Bible tells us that the beasts represent
kingdoms so put a one in the chat if you
understand that so far the
Beast
represents a
kingdom so if these beasts according to
Bible prophet phy represent kingdoms
then we can Now understand that the mark
of the beast or the sign of the Beast is
the sign of the
Kingdom the mark of the
kingdom does this make sense so
far the mark of the beast we're not
talking about a literal Beast the Beast
is symbolic of a spefic specific Kingdom
and so so now we're looking for
something that is the special sign of a
kingdom but we still don't know what
kingdom so I'm gonna ask I I just ask
put a one in the chat if you're
following so far put a seven in the chat
if you now understand that the mark of
the beast is the mark of a
kingdom and what we're looking for then
what we need to look for next is what
kingdom
we got to understand the kingdom before
we can understand the mark so put a
seven in the chat if you're on the same
page with me thus far the mark of the
beast is really the mark of the Kingdom
because we see that a kingdom that a
beast is symbolic of a kingdom so we're
looking at at the we're looking for the
mark of a
kingdom question is what
kingdom so let's go back to the Book of
Revelation and we're going to go we're
going to stay in Chapter 13 and you're
going to notice two different beasts in
Revelation chapter 13 there is something
that you may have missed and we're going
to see this very shortly so let's go
ahead and read Revelation 13 ver1 and I
stood upon the sand of the sea and saw a
beast rise up out the sea having seven
heads and 10 horns and and upon his
horns 10 crowns and upon his heads the
name of blasphemy verse two and the
Beast which I saw was like unto a
leopard and his feet were as the feet of
a bear and his mouth as the mouth of a
lion and the dragon gave him his power
and his seed and his great Authority
verse
three I saw one of his wounds as it were
wounded to death and his deadly wound
was healed and all the world wondered
after the Beast so let's let's pause for
a second now we're not going to get into
who this first Beast is that's not the
purpose of the study today and you might
be saying well Pastor how can we
even go any further if we don't know who
this first Beast is well just pause for
a second all I'm going to say about this
first Beast is that uh like Clint just
said in the chat it's an
amalgamation of the four beasts that we
saw in
Daniel and those four beasts represent
kingdoms including the tanah horns and
the little horn represent kingdoms that
arose in the past so Revelation 13 the
first Beast represents a a an
amalgamation of several kingdoms that
Rose in the past one of those being a
spiritual Kingdom which we do not need
to get into right now because that's not
the point of this message let's go ahead
and discover now a second beast in
Revelation chapter 13 Revelation 131 and
12 the Bible says and I beheld another
Beast coming up out of the earth and he
had two horns like a lamb and he spake
as a dragon he EX exercise all the power
of the first Beast before him and cause
the Earth and them that dwell therein to
worship the first Beast whose deadly
wound was healed so what we see here is
that there is a second beast that rises
after the first Beast this second beast
is rising up out of the
earth it looks like a lamb but speaks
like a dragon now again uh we're not
going to spend a whole lot of time
figuring out who this second beast is
because the purpose of our study today
believe it or not is not to determine
who these beasts are it is to deser to
determine this
Kingdom now know some of you like like
wait a minute Pastor what well there's
only two beasts in Revelation chapter
13 but I need y'all to catch something I
need y'all to pay attention to this I
need you to watch this carefully notice
with me notice with me Revelation 13
verse 13 He doeth great wonders so that
he maketh Fire come down on the earth
and a sight of men now watch this and
deceiveth them that dwell on the Earth
by the means of those Miracles which he
had power to do in the sight of the
Beast saying to them that dwell on the
earth that they should make an image to
the Beast which had the wound By The
Sword and did live
so so now in Revelation
13:14 we're seeing that this second
beast the beast from the
earth through some kind of miraculous
intervention encourages or leads the
whole world to make an
image to the first
Beast
okay let me read that again let's go
back to the screen
again verse
14 and deceiveth them that dwell on the
Earth by the means of those Miracles
which he had power to do in the sight of
the Beast saying to them that dwell on
the earth that they should make an image
to the Beast which had the wound By The
Sword and did live okay so the first
Beast watch this now the first Beast is
the Beast that had the wound by the
sword that's the beast from the sea the
second beast is the beast from the earth
and the Bible says that this Beast helps
create an image to the first Beast now
let me ask you a question and I need
y'all to think carefully with
me if I have an image of me is the image
me yes or
no if I have an if someone makes an
image of me is the image me or is the
image something separate from me though
it looks like me yes or no right the
image is not me so when the Bible says
that this second beast or Kingdom
whoever this kingdom is again we're not
even concerning ourselves with that in
this study this second
Kingdom creates an image to the first
Kingdom meaning it is not the first
Kingdom it is not the first
Beast it is a replica of the first beast
but it is not the first Beast it is not
that Kingdom that reigned in the past
that ruled in the
past now let me ask you another question
what does the image look
like just give me I need one word it
looks like a
what the
image that the second
beast makes the whole world created or
lead leads the whole word to create it
looks like what just give me one word
it's a general
word if someone made an image of me or
you that image would resemble a what a
human are y'all with me it would rep it
would it would it would look like a
human but to make an image to a beast
the image must look like
a very good zodwa it will look like a
beast
so now watch this
carefully this Beast is not the first
Kingdom it's not the first Beast even
though it looks like it it's not the
first beast and it's not even the second
beast it's another Beast put that put
put a put a one in the chat if you
understand what I'm saying because this
is going to be crucial to your
understanding of the mark so there is a
first Beast that has a deadly wound that
is healed there's a second beast that
creates an image to the first beast but
the image is not the first
Beast so in other words if the Beast is
a kingdom if the first Beast is a
kingdom and the second beast is a
kingdom well the second beast creates an
image that looks like the first Beast
meaning the second beast creates
something that looks like a beast but it
is neither the first Beast nor the
second beast meaning it's another
Beast even though it's just an image
it's another Beast are you with me give
me a five in the chat if you're with
me so if I could rephrase it this way
we're not looking for the kingdom of the
past we're not looking for a kingdom
that is presently ruling this second
beast that rises from the Earth we're
looking for a a coming
Kingdom now now watch this because in
verse uh of 15 notice what the Bible
says in verse 15 it doesn't remain just
an image the Bible says he had power to
give life unto the image of the Beast
that the image of the Beast should both
speak and cause that as many as would
not worship the image of the Beast
should be killed
so here's the question
y'all if at first it was just an image
of a beast so just imagine you know you
create an image that looks like a beast
and now suddenly the image comes to life
what is it now put that word in the chat
for me what is it now if I make a a fake
Beast it it doesn't have life you could
tell that's a fake beast but now if I
give life to the Beast it actually
becomes a what
it becomes a beast John it becomes a
beast so what we're being told here is
that if a beast represents a kingdom
we're not looking to the Past for a
kingdom we're not looking at the present
time for Kingdom the Bible is telling us
that there is a kingdom coming who will
have a special Mark a kingdom coming
that will have a special Mark that is
designated for that Kingdom
seven in the chat if y'all are following
me thus
far the Bible is warning us of a coming
kingdom yes Michelle a third Kingdom a
coming Kingdom that is not here yet and
when this Kingdom gets here it's going
to have a special sign that goes along
with it a special Mark that goes along
with it
so what do we
learn from
this number
one the
Mark or the sign of the
Kingdom has not yet come why why do we
know that the Mark is not yet here
because the kingdom which is going to be
a part of which is going to represent is
not yet
here we're going to discover what this
kingdom is but what we can know is that
the kingdom is not this coming Kingdom
whatever it is is not yet here the Mark
is going to be of this Beast or of this
Kingdom but it is not the first Kingdom
it is not the second Kingdom it is a
kingdom to come
number two so that's number one point
number one point number two that I want
you to understand is this that the Mark
is a
worldwide phenomenon the Mark is a
worldwide phenomenon come with me back
to the
screen the Bible says um verse uh
Revelation 13 verse 16 and he causeth
all all
all both small and great rich and poor
free and bond to receive a mark in their
right hand or in their forehead so what
does this tell
us it tells us beloved that the
mark of this Kingdom will be a universal
mark because
all are going to receive this Mark
except for a select group of people all
are going to receive this Mark this Mark
is a worldwide phenomenon meaning the
kingdom will be a worldwide Kingdom put
a one in the chat if you're following
me the kingdom that is coming will have
worldwide influence why because the mark
of this Kingdom that is coming will be a
worldwide mark
I also want you to
notice that the whole world will be
deceived into receiving this
Mark thus watch again it is a world wide
deception that leads to the setting up
of this Kingdom let me read it again
Revelation 13 verse3 and he doeth great
wonders so that he maketh Fire come down
from the Earth from Heaven on the earth
in the sight of men and deceiveth them
that dwell on the Earth by the means of
those Miracles which he had power to do
in the sight of the Beast saying to them
that dwell on the earth that they should
make an image to the Beast which had the
wound by a sword and did live so so
follow me here follow me
here it is through the miracle some kind
of miracle that the whole world will
witness that will ultimately lead to the
establishment of this Kingdom which is
an image of previous kingdoms of a
previous Kingdom it's a worldwide
Kingdom it will Le it will be a
worldwide deception that leads to the
setting up of this Kingdom and there
will be a Mark that goes hand inand with
this worldwide Kingdom a kingdom
that is not yet
here and some of y'all are already
catching this some of you are already
jumping ahead so here's the question
that what is a deception a deception
okay let's say that I came into to you I
came in here today and was like hey guys
I am uh I am
a uh I am a
a
cow would any of you be deceived by
that I am a
cow the reason that would not be a
deception is because there's nothing to
be deceived about you're looking at me
you see I'm a human you know I'm not a
cow there's no deception there a
deception is something that that that
leads a person to believe one thing when
the actuality is something
else meaning this kingdom is going to be
based upon a deception it's going to
look like one thing when it's actually
something
else so now all we got to do is ask
ourselves a very simple question did
Jesus warn of deception to come in in
the end of time the answer is yes and
you're going to find very interestingly
that every time Jesus warned about
deception it was regarding the very same
thing are youall ready watch this let's
go to the screen M Mark 13:
21 and then if any man shall say to you
Lo here is Christ or Lo he is there
believe him not for false christs and
false prophets shall arise and show
signs and wonders to seduce or deceive
if were possible even the
elect Matthew 244 and 5 Jesus answered
and said unto them take heed that no man
deceive you for many shall come in my
name saying I am Christ and shall
deceive
many Matthew 24:1 and many false
prophets shall deceive
many Matthew 24:24 for there shall arise
false Christ and false prophets and
shall show great signs and wonders in so
much that if it were possible they shall
deceive
the very
elect Mark chapter 135 and 6 Jesus
answered them began Jesus answering them
began to say take heed lest any man
deceive you for many shall come in my
name saying I am Christ and shall
deceive many Luke 21 take heed that you
be not deceived for many shall come in
my name saying I am Christ and the time
draweth near go ye not therefore after
them so follow me here
Jesus continually warned of of counter
of a counterfeit of
himself put a one in the chat if you're
following this Jesus continually warned
of a counterfeit of himself so here's
what we know th then about this coming
Kingdom that is not yet here it is
coming it will have to do with a
counterfeit Kingdom and a counterfeit
who or a counterfeit
what a
counterfeit
Christ a counterfeit Kingdom and a
counterfeit Christ and now you can begin
to see how the world would be
deceived by such a
kingdom let's put it together
counterfeit Kingdom counterfeit
Christ if we put that together
counterfeiting
Christ's
Kingdom a coming counterfeit Kingdom of
Christ that is worldwide that will be
ushered in by a miracle that if possible
would deceive the very elect
are y'all with me so far please notice
Matthew chapter 16:28 verily I say unto
you there be some standing here which
shall not taste this death till they see
the what son of man coming in his
kingdom son of man coming in his kingdom
so I want you to note how the son of man
Jesus his second coming and is coming in
his kingdom are tied
together why is this crucial for for us
to understand when we're talking about
this coming Kingdom because now that we
understand wait a minute so these the
these two beasts in Revelation chapter
13 are essentially going to be working
together to produce this third Kingdom a
coming Kingdom a kingdom that is not
here yet but when it comes it's going to
counterfit what is it going to
counterfeit well Jesus already warned us
of a counterfeit Christ at the end of
time but let me ask you
this what about the kingdom of
God please note with me in Daniel
chapter 2 Daniel chapter 2 and verse 44
the Bible says here Daniel is explaining
a vision that NE a dream that
Nebuchadnezzar had it was a dream of
different kingdoms Babylon Meo Persia
Greece Rome and at the end of this
vision of a statue of a man uh the a
stone is cut out without hands that
destroys the image on its feet and
notice what Daniel 2:44 says in the days
of these Kings shall the god of Heaven
set up a what set up a what everyone set
up a kingdom which shall never be
destroyed so come back here come back
with me we now
see that that
that God is going to set a kingdom up on
Earth at some point in time we're not
told in this verse we just know that
he's setting up a kingdom so hold on
wait a minute Pastor are you saying then
that before God sets up his kingdom on
Earth Satan is going to come seeking to
impersonate Christ and set up a
counterfeit Beast a counterfeit kingdom
yes that's exactly what I'm telling you
in fact if we go to Isaiah chapter 14
and notice with me what Lucifer tried to
pull off in heaven the ible says how
artart thou fallen from Heaven oh
Lucifer son of the morning how art thou
cut down to the ground which did weaken
the Nations for thou has said in thine
heart I will Ascend into heaven I will
exalt my throne above the stars of God I
will sit also upon the Mount of the
congregation in the sides of the
north I will Ascend above the heights of
the clouds I will be like the most high
Lucifer wanted to sit on God's throne in
heaven he wanted to be worshiped as God
in in heaven but he got kicked out of
heaven and lo and behold what we're
going to find is that Lucifer will
eventually attempt to do the same thing
on earth and that is what Revelation is
13 is talking about that is the coming
Kingdom where is the size of the north
please note with me the book of Psalm
4248 vers1 the Bible says notice this
great is the Lord and greatly to be
praised in the the city of our God in
the mountain of his Holiness beautiful
for situation the the joy of the whole
earth is Mount Zion on the sides of the
north the city of the great king so
listen to me you guys Satan himself we
will see is going to attempt to set up a
kingdom on Earth sitting on the sides of
the north claiming that this is God's
kingdom come to Earth and I am God
he will make it appear that the prayers
of generations has been answered when we
read Matthew 610 which says thy kingdom
come thy will be done in earth as it is
in heaven the devil is going to make it
appear the devil is going to make it
appear
that God's kingdom has come come on
Earth how y'all doing so
far we Now understand we Now understand
that the
kingdom that is coming is a counterfeit
Kingdom with a counterfeit
Christ and you might wonder well how is
the whole world going to be deceived by
that because listen y
the only the whole world is going to be
on the same page and the only way that
the whole world can get on the same page
about anything is that it must take a
miracle and that's why the Bible says
that it was by means of Miracles that he
convinces the whole world so what this
is saying beloved is that Muslims will
no longer be Muslims what are they going
to be they're going to be
Christians Buddhists are no longer going
to be Buddhists a aist are no longer
going to be ath atheist agnostics are no
longer going to be agnostics because
this miracle will be so overwhelming
will be so powerful that it will
convince all these other religions that
this must be the True Religion because
look at this miracle that cannot be
explained hence the Bible tells us in 2
Thessalonians chapter 2 verse 3 and 4
let no man deceive you by any means for
that day shall not come except there
come a falling away first and that man
of sin be revealed
the son of predition watch this who
opposes and exalteth himself above all
that is called God or that is worship so
that he as God sits in the temple of God
showing himself that he is God now why
does Satan want to do this it's very
simple you see in Romans chapter 14:1
the Bible says for it is written as I
live say the Lord every knee shall bow
to me and every tongue shall confess to
God come back
I need you to understand that worship
means to bow down the reason why Satan
what the Bible tells us that the whole
world will
worship the mark of the beast it has to
do with
worship and Satan wants the worship that
belongs to God and God says every knee
is going to bow to me all are going to
worship before me so what does Satan
want to do he wants to come as God to
take the glory of God put one in the
chat if y'all understand what I'm
saying he wants to come as God so that
every knee will bow to
him and so now we can begin to
understand something that is crucial to
to to to to getting a clear picture of
this you see when Jesus comes again
he comes in a very particular way notice
with me Revelation chapter 20 Revelation
chapter 20 which speaks about the
Millennium this Thousand-Year period of
Peace the Bible says that Satan is cast
into a bottomless pit and he shut up and
a seal is set upon him that he should
deceive the Nations no more till the
Thousand Years should be fulfilled and
after that he must be loose little
season and I saw Thrones and they sat
upon them and judgment was given unto
them them and I saw the souls of them
that were beheaded for witness of Jesus
and for the word of God and which had
not worshiped the Beast neither his
image neither had received his Mark upon
their foreheads or in their hands and
they lived and reigned with Christ a
thousand years now here's what I want
y'all to
understand the common view of the
Millennium this 10,000 years of peace is
that it occurs on Earth that's not what
the Bible teaches we don't have time to
get into that today just go back and
watch my previous sermon on the
Millennium what I want you to understand
here is that when Jesus returns the
second time he is not coming back to set
up a kingdom on Earth the Millennium the
10,000 years of
peace is not what most people think it
is this 1,000 year when Jesus let me put
it this way when Jesus returns notice
what 1 Thessalonians chapter 4:16 says
it says for the Lord him El shall
descend from heaven with a shout with
the voice of the Archangel and with the
Trump of God and the dead in Christ
shall rise first why are the dead in
Christ Rising let's keep
reading it goes on to say then we were
to our alive and remain shall be caught
up together with them in the clouds to
meet the Lord in the air and so shall we
ever be with the Lord I need y'all to
understand this that when Jesus comes
again
his people are going to be caught up to
him why because they're going with him
to Heaven he's not setting up a kingdom
here on Earth that's why his feet don't
touch the ground he stops midair and
calls the righteous up to meet him and
the Bible says in John chapter 14 it
says this let not your heart be troubled
you believe in God believe also in me in
my father's house are many mansions if
it were not so I would have told you I
go to prepare a place for you
and if I go and prepare a place for you
I will come again and receive you unto
myself that where I am there you may be
also in other words beloved Jesus
clearly said that when he returns he is
not coming to set up a kingdom on Earth
no no no he is coming to take his people
to Heaven why is this crucial to
understand because Beloved the devil
wants you to think that when Jesus comes
again he will initially set up a kingdom
on Earth why because that sets the world
up for the
counterfeit that sets the world up to
receive a Christ that is not really
Christ because Christ's Feet Don't touch
the
ground when the Bible says in Revelation
chap 13: 133 he doeth great wonders so
that he maketh Fire come down from from
Heaven on the earth in the sight of men
and need y'all to understand what this
fire is because in Hebrews 12:29 the
Bible says our God is a consuming fire
in Isaiah 66:15 it says for behold the
Lord will come with fire and with his
chariots like a whirlwind to render his
anger with Fury and his rebuke with
flames of fire so in other words Beloved
the miracle here is the appearing of
what looks like Jesus but isn't Jesus
it's a counterfeit Second Coming where
Satan himself will appear as Christ will
claim that he has come to set up peace
on Earth a thousand years of peace that
this is the millennial Kingdom and
whoever is down with this Kingdom will
receive the mark of his kingdom they
will see it as a sign that they are
connected with the god of Heaven
are y'all following
this this is why the Bible says in 1
Thessalonians 53 it says for when they
shall say peace and safety then sudden
destruction cometh upon them as travail
upon a woman with child and they shall
not Escape why would they be seeing
peace and safety look at the world right
now can anyone say in the time we're
living right now that there is peace and
safety or that there will ever be peace
and safety
no no no no no the only way people will
be deceived into thinking peace and
safety watch this let me just let me
just let me just put the verse up on the
screen notice with me notice with me
Jeremiah 23 verse5 behold the days come
say the Lord that I will raise unto
David A righteous branch and a king
shall reign and prosper and shall
execute judgment and Justice in the
earth verse 6
it says in his days Judah shall be saved
and Israel shall dwell safely and this
is his name whereby he shall be called
the Lord our righteousness I want y'all
to understand beloved that that when
Satan comes as Christ he's going to
claim to be here to set up a thousand
years of peace and this is when the
whole world will be saying peace and
safety look Jesus is with us he's here
Muslims who did not believe what the
Bible said are now going to be deceived
into thinking oh well this must be the
Christ because look at this miracle and
Buddhist and atheist the whole world
because of this miracle of fire the
whole world is going to be in line with
this coming Kingdom that is set up on
the
earth so then the deception has to do
with the counter with the counter in of
Christ it has to do with the
counterfeiting of a kingdom which must
mean then that the mark of the kingdom
is a counterfeit as
well did y'all catch that if the kingdom
is a counterfeit and the head of the
kingdom is a counterfeit then the mark
of the Kingdom must be a counterfeit now
please follow this beloved because if
the kingdom appears to be
good and the king of this coming King
kingom appears to be
good then the mark of the coming Kingdom
will also what
appear put it in the chat for me
please it will also appear to be
good this is why Jesus warned us in John
16:2 they shall put you out of the
synagogues yay the time cometh that
whosoever ever kth you will think he is
doing God a
service come on y'all let's
recap the Mark is not here yet because
this kingdom is not here
yet the Mark will be a test of loyalty
to the kingdom of
God in other words the mark may not look
like something openly
bad however the mark requires watch this
listen carefully y'all the mark requires
not a worldwide conversion of money but
a worldwide conversion of souls let me
say that
again the Mark will require a worldwide
conversion not of
money but of
souls in other words the it
some people think in order for the mark
to come about there has to be a One
World Currency no no no no no no no no
no no no in order for the mark to come
up out the whole world has to be
converted converted to what they think
is something good a religious
conversion everybody's going to be on
the same page regarding this Kingdom and
what's so interesting is that there's so
many different religions that believe
that there's going to be this period of
peace on
Earth which beloved is not what the
Bible teaches when it comes to the
Millennium the mark that then beloved is
a religious one not a financial one let
me say it again the Mark is a religious
one not a financial one it is a sign
that says I am in Allegiance with this
Kingdom I am down with this Kingdom I
believe that this is the Christ I
believe that this is his kingdom and I
believe all that he
says that's why the Bible says in
Revelation 13:6 it says and as many as
would not worship as many as would not
worship the image of the Beast should be
killed and he causeth all both small and
great rich and poor now let's so so
watch this y'all you see how it's about
worship
now
listen now that we got the kingdom down
now that we understand what the kingdom
is now we're ready to understand what
the Mark is we got the kingdom it's a
coming Kingdom the kingdom is not here
yet but when this kingdom comes it'll be
a counterfeit Kingdom with a counterfeit
Christ brought in by counterfeit by
counterfeit Miracles designed to deceive
the whole world if possible even the
elect will be like like oh this is
Jesus now to be down with this Kingdom
you're going to have to have this Mark
it will be a sign of allegiance to the
kingdom that this kingdom is good it is
of god
Etc so let's watch this so the Bible
says in Revelation 13:16 we just had on
the screen he causeth all and I want to
look at that word cause just for a
moment the the the the Greek word poo to
cause I want you to notice what the
strong concordance has for the various
meanings of the word
cause
agree band together commit
fulfill cause or keep
observe
perform transgress the
law transgress the law wait
what so he C it causeth meaning he's
going to make all agree he's going to
make all band together he's going to
make all commit to something he's going
to make all seek to fulfill something
he's going to make all seek to keep
something observe something perform
something that also has to do with
transgressing the
law now why is it so interesting because
that very same word is used in this
verse 1 John 3 verse4 which says this
whosoever committed sin and then you see
that term there transgresseth also the
law those four words those four words
are the they are translated it is the
same Greek word that we just saw that is
translated as cause in Revelation
chapter
13 so whosoever committed Comm Comm sin
transgresses also the law for sin is the
transgression of the law so let me ask
you something can we Now
understand that whatever this Mark is it
has something to do with
transgressing God's
law committing to something that is
outside the will of
God are y'all following
me whatever this is it has to do with
transgressing the law of God because the
Bible says sin is the transgression of
the
law now why is that so interesting why
is this so interesting because in Isaiah
chapter 8 and verse 16 in fact let me do
this verse so that Hebrew word katham or
tatham is the word used for
seal it's it's the word used for seal in
the Old Testament and it means to close
up especially to seal to make an end to
Mark to seal to stop up in essence it's
the same thing as the mark uh used in
Revelation chapter 13 a seal and a mark
are the same thing now why is it
significant because the devil wants to
Mark those who transgress the law but
notice what Isaiah 8:16 says which uses
this very word for Mark bind up the
testimony seal or Mark the law among my
disciples now did y'all catch that come
back come on
y'all the devil wants to cause meaning
transgress the law while God says seal
my disciples seal my disciples with the
law so on one hand you have God saying
here are those that keep the
Commandments of God and on the other
hand Satan is marking those who are who
are somehow transgressing or or or
keeping something that is not in
accordance with the law of
God so whatever we know this Mark of the
Kingdom or mark of the beast will be
something that is that that will H show
allegiance to the kingdom of Satan which
will appear to be the kingdom of God but
whatever that is it will be in direct it
will be a direct contradiction to the
law of
God this is why Proverbs 7 verse1 reads
this my son keep my words and lay up my
Commandments with thee keep my
Commandments and live and my law as the
apple of thine
eye bind them upon thy fingers wait what
bind them upon thy fingers write them on
the table of thine heart say unto wisdom
Thou Art my sister and call
understanding thy kinswoman that they
may keep thee from the strange woman
from The Stranger which which flattereth
with her words you do understand that in
the Book of Revelation Babylon mystery
Babylon is described as a woman and
ultimately the final version of Babylon
the final version of
will be this coming Kingdom that is not
yet set
up but when it is set up God says keep
my
Commandments that you may avoid the
smooth words of this mystery system of
this false system this system that
professes to be the bride of Christ but
really is something totally different
come with me Revelation 14:9 Revelation
14:9 the Bible says and the third Angel
followed the third Angel followed them
saying with a loud voice if any man
worship the Beast and his If any man
worship the beast in His image and
receive his Mark in his forehead or in
his hand the same shall drink of the
wine of the Wrath and I'm just gonna
let's just so I want you to know here
where do they receive the mark in the
forehead or in the hand and then the the
warning ends like this here here is the
patience of the Saints here are they
that keep the Commandments of God and
have the faith of Jesus so I need y'all
to see how in two verses earlier you
have a warning against the mark and then
you have here's the patience of the
Saints here are they that keep the
Commandments of God so those that keep
the Commandments of God are are are are
separated from those who receive the
mark whatever the Mark is it must have
something to do with the Commandments of
God can we verify this with the Bible
the answer is absolutely yes Deuteronomy
chapter 6 and verse eight the Bible
says and thou talking about the law of
God shall bind them for a sign a mark a
sign a mark a symbol Thou shalt bind
them for a sign where on your hand and
they shall be frontlets between your
eyes let me read again again Exodus 39
it shall be a sign unto thee upon thine
hand and for a memorial between thine
eyes that the Lord's law may be in thy
mouth for with a strong hand the Lord
brought thee out of Egypt now I need
y'all to catch this I need y'all to
follow this because God said put the
law put the
law in your mind and in your hand
interestingly the Mark is given or
received in the mind or in the hand so
we are just seeing beloved uh scripture
after scripture demonstrating first this
is the kingdom that's coming this is the
Beast that is coming it is the mark of
the beast meaning the mark of this
Kingdom and this Mark will appear to be
an a sign of allegiance to Christ when
in actuality it isn't
it is a counterfeit of the law of
God here's what's
interesting uh let's go to the
screen and um you're going to read
something about what the old what the
what the far or the Jews did in in back
in ancient times the hand
fctory has only one compartment which
contains the four biblical selections
written upon a single SHP of parchment
in four parallel columns and in the
order given in the Bible
the head Fel uh the head fatory has four
compartments formed from one piece of
leather in each of which was one
selection written on a separate piece of
parchment and it is is deposited
perpendicularly let me keep reading the
head fctory I'm sorry we got one more
one
more here we go if one is Left-Handed he
lays the hand filter on the same place
on his right hand come back to the
screen with me y'all I just need you to
see that God's
law was to
be written in the
mind and upon our hands and the Jews
took it literally we got to put a seal
we got to put a a mark a symbol on our
foreheads and a symbol on our hands and
this is what they did you see the
picture right here let's go back to the
screen real quick you see the the
picture of how they did this right so
they would put the sign on the hand put
the sign on the forehead to show that
they were in Allegiance with God's
law so so now that we know let's come
back now that we know that the law of
God that the that the the the coming
kingdom is a counterfeit Kingdom with a
counterfeit
Christ and the Mark has something to do
with going against or transgressing the
law of God now we simply got to ask
ourselves a question well what
law and here's my answer for
you is there a Commandment that God
spoke regarding this would be the sign
of universal
worship a sign of every knee bowing
before him what do you think what is
there a law a a particular law that God
says in the New Kingdom this is what
everybody's going to be doing and it'll
be a symbol of All Flesh coming before
me to worship the answer is yes I need
you to check it out it's found in the
book of Isaiah chap 66 verse 22 notice
what it says for as the new heavens and
the new Earth which I shall make will
remain before me sayith the Lord so
shall your seed and your name remain and
it shall come to pass that from one new
moon to another and from one Sabbath to
another shall All Flesh come before me
to worship
say it the
Lord so here's what we know in the
actual New Kingdom Come On In the actual
New Kingdom not the fake one the actual
New Kingdom the Sabbath will be that
special worship where everyone comes
every knee
bows come on every knee bows before God
Sabbath by Sabbath every Sabbath the
entire universe will come before God
that's in the real
Kingdom so it would make sense then that
Satan in order to attempt to get the
whole world to bow to him in his quote
unquote New Kingdom that he's going to
set up on this Earth to deceive the
whole world guess
what guess what he's going to have his
own
law but it's not going to be the Sabbath
it will be a counterfeit of the Sabbath
it will be something that is in place of
that is directly opposed to the Sabbath
that may look like the Sabbath but
actually
isn't and now you can begin to
understand why the Bible says and all
that dwell upon the Earth shall worship
Him whose names are not written in the
Book of Life of the lamb slain from the
foundation of the world you see beloved
you're breaking the first four
Commandments if you end up worship
worshiping in this Kingdom because
you're number one you're worshiping
another God other than God number two
you're worshiping an image an image an
image of God number three the name of
the Lord is being used in vain to be
connected to someone that is not the
Lord and you're worshiping that being
and number four there is a false Sabbath
a f a false Comm a false Sabbath that
will be
used to show allegiance to to this
Kingdom what I need you to understand
beloved is is that this false Sabbath is
not now the mark of the beast don't
think wait a minute I'm not keeping the
genuine Sabbath the true Sabbath have I
received the mark no it is when this
kingdom
comes that's when it becomes a test
question in this
Kingdom Pastor what do you mean a false
Sabbath please let me break this down in
Exodus 20 verse 8 the Bible says
remember the Sabbath day to keep it holy
six days sh th labor and do all thy work
but the seventh day is the Sabbath of
the Lord thy God in it Thou shalt not do
any work thou nor thy son nor thy
daughter thy man servant nor thy maid
servant nor thy cattle nor thy stranger
that is within thy gates for in six days
the Lord made Heaven and Earth the sea
and The Fountains of water and all that
in them is and rested the seventh day
wherefore the Lord bless the Sabbath day
and hallowed it now I need y'all to
understand something you see a seal is a
device for making an impression in wax
clay paper or some other medium
including an embossment on paper and is
also the impression thus made the
original purpose of a seal was to
authenticate a
document you
guys the purpose of a seal is to
authenticate a
document and what I need you to
understand beloved is that when God gave
the
Sabbath he was giving the sign of his
work it was the sign that he owned this
world
y'all want to see something Powerful 2
Timothy chapter 2: 19 the Bible says
here nevertheless the foundation of God
standeth sure having this seal the Lord
knoweth them that are his and let
everyone that nameth the name of Christ
depart from iniquity I need y'all to
catch this this verse is telling us that
the the Lord's seal helps determine
who's are his and who are
not Albert Barnes say of of this very
reverse the illusion is to the custom in
rearing an edifice of inscribing the
name of the Builder and the design of
the edifice on the
cornerstone I need y'all to understand
this God when he creates the Earth he
uses the Sabbath as his seal the sign of
his authority
the
Sabbath is the Seal of the document of
the law of
God when you look at the Ten
Commandments the Sabbath right there in
the middle of The Commandments is the
seal because it is a Commandment that
actually gives God's name his his title
as Creator and his territory y'all need
to catch this you see a seal all seals
look at the screen government seals look
like this
there is the the title and the
territory and what you need to
understand is that the Sabbath reveals
the title of God as our creator and his
territory the heavens and the Earth he
affixes the same seal to the heart and
mind of those that belong to him this is
why he says notice with me Exodus
31:13 speak thou unto to the children of
Israel saying verily my sabbaths you
shall keep for it is a sign between me
and you throughout your Generations that
you may know that I am the Lord that
doth sanctify you and Ezekiel 20:2
moreover also I gave them my sabbaths to
be a sign between me and them that they
might know that I am the Lord that
sanctifies them please listen to
me the Sabbath is a sign that God
sanctifies you and you don't sanctify
yourself the Sabbath is a sign that we
depend upon God for our sanctification
and beloved listen if you understand the
importance of sanctification you will
clearly see that the Sabbath is
synonymous with sanctification why
because when you go to Genesis chapter
2:3 the first time God sanctifies
something it's the Sabbath God blessed
the seventh day and Sanctified it
because that in it he had rested from
his work which God created and made the
Sabbath beloved is the sign of God's
sanctifying
power that's why the devil hates this
particular commandment so
much this is what Satan will counterfeit
when his kingdom comes he wants to claim
the whole earth as his this is my world
not God I know the Sabbath there says
God is a creator of the Heaven and the
Earth but I want that worship that
belongs to God so I'm G to come with my
own
Sabbath I'm G to come with my own seal
that will appear to be the sign of my
kingdom and I'm going to counterfeit I'm
going to make myself look like Christ
I'm going to counterfeit this Kingdom
and listen all who worship me from every
first day of the week to every first day
of the week the the the the the the
so-called Sabbath that replace God's
genuine sabath Sabbath on the seventh
day and the whole world because of the
miracle working power of this deception
will bow listen I need to break this
down and we are we are almost there guys
we are almost there listen to
me you see Romans chapter 16 verse 16
lays out a very powerful principle it
says know ye not that to whom you yield
yourself servants to obey his servants
you are to whom you obey whether of sin
unto death or of obedience unto
righteousness you need to understand
beloved that the issue is not over the
Commandment of Sabbath versus some other
day the issue is who you obey if God
were to tell you to stand up and the
devil said nah you should sit down there
is no sin in and of itself in standing
up or sitting down but who you listen
to who you listen to can determine your
faith because who you listen to you're
saying I'm his servant and so you see a
seal or a Mark says this is my servant
this is my servant it's not I like yes M
it's not about the day so much as it is
about who you obey so if God says seven
and the Devil comes along through this
guy let's go to Daniel 7:25 because the
Bible forewarned that that first Kingdom
that we read about in Revelation 13 the
first king the the Kingdom from the from
the sea the Bible warns that this
Kingdom would speak great words against
the most high wear out the Saints of the
most high and think to change times and
laws come
on God forewarned of the attempt to
change his law and in this coming
Kingdom at the very end of time this
coming kingdom is going to take that
same change and say listen all who truly
love you know how the Bible says in John
14:15 if you love me keep my
Commandments this is exactly what Satan
is going to say in the name of Jesus if
you love me keep my Commandments and one
of those Commandments is going to be a
Commandment that goes against the direct
commandment of
God and those who have been who have not
taken the time to study the word of God
those who have not taken the time to ask
God what is his will those who have not
taken the time to say I will not follow
what man says or what the majority says
but I'm going to do what the word of God
says those who have not taken the time
to study the truth of God God's word are
going to be deceived by this counterfeit
coming they're going to be be deceived
by this counterfeit Christ they're going
to be deceived by this counterfeit
Kingdom and they're going to be deceived
by this counterfeit Mark and they will
think it's all good they will say oh the
Sabbath that was done away with you know
my pastor told me that and look at
everybody around me everybody's going to
church on the first day of the week the
Sabbath that's for the Jews listen in
Isaiah 56 the Bible says also the sons
of the strangers that join themselves to
the Lord and to serve him and to love
the name of the Lord to be his servants
everyone that keepeth the Sabbath from
polluting it and taketh hold of my
Covenant God is clearly pointing out
here that even the Gentiles were invited
to keep the Sabbath
I hope y'all are catching this
y'all I hope y'all are getting this come
on we are almost there I promise you we
are almost there look we're about to
wrap this thing up in Nehemiah chapter 9
I need y'all to see this in Nehemiah
chapter n after the children of Israel
have been disobedient to the will of God
you find this very peculiar verse it
says because of all this we make a sure
Covenant and write it and our princes
Levites and Priests and seal unto it so
because of their Rebellion they're now
saying that because of all our rebellion
and we were go we were sent into
captivity now we're back we're going to
make a covenant and we're going to seal
unto it and in this
Covenant one of the things described
that they were going to do it says and
if the people of the land bring wear or
any victuals on the Sabbath day to sell
we would not buy it of them on the
Sabbath day or on the holy day so they
made a covenant
that anyone found buying or selling on
the
Sabbath would be in some pretty serious
trouble do you understand that when the
Devil comes to set up his counterfeit
Kingdom he's just he's going to do the
exact opposite if we find anyone
breaking this sabbath the Sabbath of
this Kingdom the Sabbath of the New
Covenant and he will dress it up in
every way possible and even use
scriptures to try to justify and those
who have not been studying those who are
unaware of Satan's devices they're going
to what reason would they have to think
this is anything
dangerous Revelation 22:14 the Bible
says blessed are they that do his
Commandments that they may have right to
the tree of life and may enter in
through the gates into the city this is
super significant beloved because
remember at the very beginning of
Mankind's History Adam and Eve were put
out of the garden why because in Genesis
21:16 God gave a test God gave a test in
his
kingdom the Lord God commanded the man
saying of every tree of the garden thou
May freely eat but of the tree of the
knowledge of Good and Evil Thou shalt
not eat of it for in the day thou eatest
thereof thou shal surely die I need you
to understand that the test that God
gave was a very simple test my
kingdom here's my test a simple test
here's a tree you can eat from here's a
tree you cannot eat from it was not a
huge test it was not a you know it
wasn't like killing it was just simply
eating from a
tree can you imagine people saying oh
you know what's the big deal with eating
from a tree it wasn't about the tree it
was about who you obey who Adam and Eve
were willing to obey it wasn't the the
the test itself it wasn't the the the
you know what made up the test it was
who are you going to obey so God says
don't eat from the tree Satan comes
along eat from the
tree it wasn't about the tree y'all it
wasn't about the
tree it was about obedience who you g to
obey so in light of that they were put
out of the garden they had no right to
the Tree of Life well the Bible says at
the end of time there will be people who
have right to the Tree of Life why
because they're keeping the Commandments
and watch this Satan's F in this coming
Kingdom Satan's going to have a test and
what is that
test receive the
Mark we
see that that Mark is going to simply be
an issue of a
day that little horn power we read in
Daniel 7:25 is responsible for changing
the Sabbath from the seventh day of the
week to the first day of the week now
listen y'all again right now it's not
the Mark it's when that kingdom
comes and now Satan says and watch this
y'all for those who are not obeying now
in a time in a time of relative in a
time of the footman when these miracles
happen how how easy do you think it's
going to be to be like you know what I
think I'm gonna follow God now follow
him now today is the day of salvation
follow him
now this is why Beloved the Bible say in
Revelation 12:17 the dragon was wroth
with the woman and went to make war with
the remnant of her seed which keep the
Commandments of God and have the
testimony of Jesus Christ beloved those
who keep the Commandments of God Satan
hates them and he is trying to do
everything in his
power to keep
them from obeying
God Hebrews chapter 10
10 Hebrews chapter 10 we got two verses
and then we're done Hebrews chap 10:1 16
the Bible says this is the Covenant that
I will make with them after those days
say the Lord I will put my laws into
their hearts and in their minds will I
write them I need y'all to listen to me
as we close this
out God is coming back for his
children put a one in the chat if you
want to be ready for the return of the
Lord put a one in the chat if you want
to be ready for the return Return of the
Lord God is coming back for his
children but but what I need you to
understand is that there will be a
paternity
test there will be a paternity test to
determine who God's children
are and in this paternity test
God is checking for
DNA he's checking to see who has the
divine nature
attributes who has the law of God
written on their hearts and in their
minds and on their fingers who are
really my children because I just need
y'all to see this 1 John 2:3 the Bible
says hereby we do know that we know him
if we keep his Commandments he that
saith I know him and keepeth not his
Commandments is a liar and the truth is
not in
him that's not my
kid that's not my
child my children obey my children keep
my Commandments my children when I tell
them this somebody else can't come along
and say oh yeah well God doesn't mean
that anymore no no no no no no no my
children hear my voice and they follow
me so please just get get this with
me to recap there's a coming Kingdom
that kingdom is going to be a
counterfeit Kingdom run by a counterfeit
Christ which is none other than Satan
himself who wanted to sit upon the sides
of the North in heaven but was kicked
out and now will attempt to do the same
thing on earth he will set up a kingdom
claiming that the kingdom of God is now
on Earth in answer to your prayers I am
the god of that Kingdom sitting in the
temple of God showing myself that I am
God and all who will not come before me
Sunday after Sunday Sabbath after
Sabbath to worship before me are going
to be
guilty of
blasphemy do not buy or sell for do not
trade with them they are going to be
punished and in fact they're going to be
killed
you're saying right now over a day
remember in the garden it was over a
tree it is not about the day anymore
than it is about the tree it is about
who you
obey and now you know why Satan don't
want didn't want you to hear this
message now you understand why and how
the whole world is being set up to be
deceived by this overmastering
delusion by talk by teaching that the
law of God no longer stands by teaching
that the Sabbath no longer stands that
by teaching that there will be a
millennium of a thousand years of peace
on Earth where everybody is getting
along where Jesus is going to set up his
kingdom on Earth all these counterfeit
erroneous teachings are setting up the
entire world to be caught off guard
by the very deceptions Jesus warned us
about
so what are you going to do with
this some of you are watching you're
like man I go I got to go study this out
please go study it
out go study it out some of you are
watching today and you're saying whoa
I'm convicted I need to start keeping
the Sabbath I'm gonna listen you need to
do that follow the leading of the spirit
and and begin to keep God's Commandments
now you cannot do it in your own
strength but Christ in
you can do it Christ has come unto me
all you that labor and are heavy laden
and I will give you rest rest from what
rest from lawlessness rest from adultery
rest from stealing rest from lying rest
from worshiping other gods rest from
taking the lord's name in vain rest from
breaking the Sabbath Beloved the Sabbath
is the sign of rest how in the world can
people teach that it is the sign of
works it makes literally no
sense so my appe my
appe my
appeal is that we will follow the lord
and his word where it leads without fear
of consequences from friends from
Family Jesus says follow
me follow
me and I will give you
rest so my slides are are available in
the chat I think where there is a uh a
QR code you can scan if you want these
slides you got them all you need to
study this on your you got it do it do
it do
it praise God do
it and I need y'all to follow
this I need y'all to do this if you're
ready to follow the lord if you if
you've watching this and you're seeing
this for the first time put that one in
the the chat to say wow this is my first
time hearing this I want to learn more
we got a
whole
playlist called the share the truth
playlist you need to go back and watch
every one of them watch the one on the
Millennium watch all the ones that have
come before this and I promise you
you're going to be enlightened your mind
is going to be open you're hearing this
for the first time you're saying look I
need to know more I need to study more
Pastor I need to connect with you put
that one in the
chat contact our B worker it's right
there living manab bwg mail.com and
we're going to do everything in our
power to bring this whole truth before
you put that one in the chat say that's
me I need to understand this more I need
to learn about this more and if you've
heard this before and you're and you're
convicted to continue walking in truth
I'm going to ask you put that to in the
chat and say yeah that's me listen if
you're if you're like okay I'm hearing
this for the first time and I want to
know this and understand it and
ultimately I I need to give my life to
the Lord and be baptized I want you to
reach out to our Bible worker same same
uh Gmail living manab bwg mail.com we'll
put it up there in the chat again and uh
listen we got you God's got you don't be
afraid to walk in the
truth don't be afraid to walk in the
truth pray with me heavenly father thank
you for speaking to us thank you for
your word thank you for your truth thank
you for opening our eyes and thank you
for laying out for us what is coming in
this socalled
Kingdom that the Book of Revelation
warns about Lord may we not be deceived
by the very things you warned us open
our eyes open our understanding and most
of all Lord give us the strength of
conviction that we may stand in the face
of what will be
overwhelming Miracles overwhelming
odds may we be willing to stand firm for
you this is our prayer in Jesus name
please bless those who are hearing this
for the first time who are wanting to
study deeper who are wanting to
understand the truth as it is in Jesus
may they be drawn to truth wherever it
leads is my prayer in Jesus name amen
and amen we want to invite you to join
us for the uh
Afterglow um we're going to put the link
right there it's uh it's a zoom link so
please join us and we will all
Fellowship um build and share thoughts
on what we've learned and may God bless
you and keep
you thank you for worshiping with us
today if this is your first time
visiting with us we invite you to check
out our website at Living mana. live
there you will learn more about our
mission to reach the world with the
Gospel of Jesus we have exciting live
programs throughout the week covering
topics like physical health Mental
Health help prayer learning how to prove
God's existence and much more if you
would like to support the ministry you
can click on the tithe and offering link
on our website we ask that you continue
to pray for the church as God continues
to open doors for our programming to
reach the world thank you again for your
prayers and your support
[Music]